極限の精神状態で ２択を迫られて それを　ぶち壊す発想ができる そこが　お前のすごいところだ
Fortunes x Aren't x Right?
次々と トリックタワーから姿を現し 久しぶりの外の空気を味わった
Kurapika!
ヘヘヘ…。
If there's anything we can do to help—
ヘヘっ。
Hey!
諸君 トリックタワー脱出　おめでとう。
You did it first. I was getting revenge!
残る試験は 第４次試験と最終試験のみ。
But I didn't do it on purpose. You did it deliberately!
第４試験は あの　ゼビル島にて行われる。 では　早速だが…。
Why are you so upset? We sold that piece for 355 million Jenny!
諸君には これから　くじを引いてもらう。
It could have sold for more... We got a decent price!
くじ？
No, we could have gotten over 400
million if we'd sold at a different time.
フン。
We had bad luck...
狩る者と　狩られる者。
You sure take this seriously.
この中には ２４枚のナンバーカード
It isn't like you would've gotten anything
if we'd gotten a better price.
すなわち　今　残っている諸君らの 受験番号が入っている。 それでは タワーを脱出した順に
That's not the issue here. If we run with the money,
we'd each get a 170 million cut!
１枚ずつ引いてもらおう。
Are you really friends with Gon and Killua?
では　１番目。
I was joking.
ねぇ　キルア。 あ？
Having only just learned Nen,
how did you manage that?
「狩る者と　狩られる者」って このメンバー同士で 戦えってこと？ ああ　多分な。
If you're looking for advice
on catching the spiders, then stop. That's not the only reason.
何だか　よく分からんが
Nen is strongly affected by your mental state.
こういうのは 気合で引くもんだぜ。
The stronger your resolve,
the more power you receive.
うりゃ！
However, you also incur a
big risk at the same time.
全員　引き終わったね。
What's the rule?
では　そのカードに貼られた シールを剥がしてもらえるかな。
If I use my chains on one who isn't a spider, I will forfeit my life.
それぞれのターゲットだ。
If I break the rule, that blade will pierce my heart, killing me.
今　諸君が 何番のカードを引いたかは
My power is the product of pure hatred. It only works on the spiders.
全て　この箱のメモリーに 記録されている。
I'm telling you because I trust you. Don't tell anyone else.
各自 自由に処分してもらって結構。
Why would you tell us something so important?!
奪うのは　ターゲットの ナンバープレートだ。
I'm not sure.
何だ 命の取り合いじゃねえのか。
With their leader's death,
I must have relaxed.
もちろん　プレートを奪う手段は 何でもあり。
It'll be fine if we keep our mouths shut. It's too dangerous.
まず　命を奪ってから ゆっくり手に入れても構わない。
One of the surviving members can read minds.
それが　一番 手っ取り早そうだな。
If they find out, Kurapika won't
be able to beat them!
そ…　そういうことかよ。
But she didn't learn anything last time.
いいか？　諸君。
That's because we didn't know
Kurapika was the chain user.
自分のターゲットとなる受験生の ナンバープレートは　３点。
Then we just have to stay away from them.
自分自身のナンバープレートも ３点。
They've already checked you,
so they think you're clean.
それ以外のナンバープレートは １点。
But there's also a guy called Nobunaga. He's especially dangerous.
最終試験に進むために 必要な点数は　６点。
He's looking for Kurapika, and he's still trying to chase us down.
ゼビル島での滞在期間中に
Is he aware that you guys know Kurapika?
６点分のナンバープレートを 集めること。
No... Then it's okay! As long as no one around the mind reader
それが　第４次ハンター試験の クリア条件だ。
knows Kurapika, then you're safe. Well, I've also been in
contact with Hisoka.
ご乗船の皆様 第３次ハンター試験 お疲れさまでした！
He knows that I am the chain user.
私　ガイドを 務めさせていただきます カラと申します！
We made a pact, but his target, the leader of
the spiders, is now dead.
当船は　これより ２時間ほどの予定で ゼビル島へ向かいます！
So I don't know what he'll do.
ここに残った２４名の方々には 来年の試験会場への
What do you mean?
無条件招待の権利が 与えられます！
We're leaving?
たとえ　今年　受からなくても 気を落とさずに
I mean exactly what I say. We're departing tonight.
来年　また 挑戦してくださいね…。
We'll take the rest of the treasure tonight.
うっ　辛気くせぇわ！
That will be the end. It isn't. What else is there?
戦いは　すでに始まっている。
We have to find the chain user.
ああ　みんな 自分のプレートは外して
You seem obsessed. Yes, I am.
懐に しまい込みやがったもんな…。
We're going to scatter
without avenging Uvo?
それでは ゼビル島に着くまでの２時間は
Uvo will be bored in the next
world if we don't send
自由時間となります。
the chain user to join him.
皆さん　船の旅を お楽しみくださいね！
Cut it out, Nobunaga. The boss has issued an order.
もしも…　もしもだ。
But is that really an order from our boss, Chrollo?
俺のターゲットが　お前だったら 俺は容赦なく　お前を狩るぜ。
Nobunaga, watch yourself... Shut up!
当然だ。
I'm talking to Chrollo!
お前のターゲットは俺なのか？
Before I can answer your question...
フッ…　「もしも」の話だ。 あぁ　そりゃ　そうなんだが…。
Nobunaga, I need you to answer my question.
そっか…。 俺のターゲットも　お前じゃないぞ！ フフ…。
よっ。
What day were you born?
お前　何番　引いた？
You already know that! The hell is this about?! What do you want next?
キルアは？ 内緒。
No, that's enough. Write all of that on this sheet of paper.
アハハ！ エヘヘ！
Why didn't you tell me to
do that in the first place?
４４番って…。
Huh? What's this? A one hundred percent accurate
fortune written in verse.
マジ？
The ability to see the future.
お前　くじ運　悪いなぁ。
I stole this power from Nostrade's daughter. One hundred percent accurate?
やっぱり？ １９９番って誰だっけ？
Each of the four verses predicts
what will happen in that week.
やっぱし　ゴンも分かんねえ？ うん。
The calendar loses a precious component.
他の奴の番号なんか 全部　覚えちゃいないもんな。
The remaining months gather to mourn.
説明　聞いてから 周り探してみたんだけどさぁ
The first moon, having missed his opportunity, continues to pursue the eleventh moon alone.
もう　みんなプレート隠してやんの せこいよなぁ。
The chrysanthemum withers and falls, to lie on the ground beside bloody Scarlet Eyes.
ゴン…。 えっ　何？
But the spider does not stop. Even after losing half its limbs.
嬉しいのか　怖いのか どっちなんだ？
This is the fortune his
daughter gave me yesterday.
両方…　かな。
Is the precious component of the calendar...
これが　もし ただの決闘だったら
Uvo.
俺に勝ち目は なかっただろうけど でも　プレートを奪えばいい ってことなら
That girl didn't know anything about Uvo.
何か　きっと方法が あるんじゃないかなってさ。
In other words, she predicted our attack
うん。
on the Mafia auction.
今の俺でも 少しはチャンスがあるって
And there were fans of her
fortunetelling among the Ten Dons.
そう思うと　確かに怖いけど
I get it.
やりがいは　あるよ。 そっか。
That explains why the merchandise had already been moved the
first time we attacked.
まっ　頑張ろうぜ。
What does Nobunaga's fortune say?
生き残れよ　ゴン。
I don't know what was written. Ask Nobunaga.
うん！　キルアもね！
Well, Nobunaga?
ゼビル島に到着です！
No idea... I can't interpret this.
それでは　第３次試験の クリアタイムが早い人から順に
I kind of understand the second verse.
下船していただきます。
The spider loses half its limbs.
チッ　またかよ！
The spider would be us?
１人が上陸してから　２分後に 次の人がスタートする方式を とります。
Yeah. And the limbs would be the members, so half would be six.
ってことは　俺達は　かなり後だな。 うん。
That means five more after losing Uvo. The same line was in my fortune.
その間に ６点分のプレートを集めて
Let me see.
また　この場所に 戻って来てください。 それでは　１番の方からスタート！
Boss, can you tell my fortune?
なるほど… 先に行けるほうが有利だな。
You join your ally as an offering, to keep him from being lonely.
ああ　自分は先に身を隠し
You will find eternal rest
狙った獲物の動向を チェックできるからな。
in a room filled with black merchandise.
２分経過！　２番の方　スタート。
Beware solitude above all.
カタカタカタ… うぅ！ カタカタカタ…
You have the most to fear when
you are alone with another.
カタカタカタ…
I thought so. I'm going to die next week.
３番の方　スタート。
Seriously? Yep.
おっしゃ！ ７番の方…。
Because I only got two verses.
１１番の方…。 １５番の方…。
And Pakunoda and Shalnark will die, as well.
２０番の方　スタート！
How do you know that?
２分経過 ２１番の方　スタート！
It seems the numbered months
here refer to Troupe members. November is the eleventh month.
じゃ！ うん！
Uvo was member #11. Exactly.
さてと…　まずは 島の様子でも探ってみるか。
It blooms in August, the eighth month, and it withers in June. This refers to members #6, #8, and #9.
２分経過　２２番の方　スタート！
And since the word "falling"
is used, it implies death.
はい！　じゃあね。 おう！
I'm not certain to whom "Scarlet Eyes" refers.
まずは　ヒソカを見つけなきゃ
I'm guessing it's the chain user.
どうやったら　あのヒソカから プレートを奪えるんだろう…
Nobunaga, this means we'll
suffer serious casualties if we fight the chain user!
) )
You and I have abilities that
can be easily replaced, but Shizuku and Pakunoda have rare powers.
)
The Troupe can't afford to lose them.
) )
Today is Saturday of the first week.
) うん…。
If we return home today, we won't run into the chain user next week.
やっぱり　とても真っ向勝負じゃ 奪えそうもないよなぁ
The advantage of being able
to predict the future
あっ
is that we can avoid undesirable prophecies.
受験者だ
If we leave this place without
fighting the chain user, this fortune is one hundred percent
certain to not come true.
後ろに　もう１人
Nobunaga, you and Uvo were
the Troupe's attackers.
前の人を狙ってるんだ ん？
To die is just part of your job. I believe that you both chose
that role voluntarily.
ハッ。
You should tell some of the
other members' fortunes.
うお！　うぅ…。 しくじった！ おっと　危ねぇ　危ねぇ。
Perhaps we could gather additional
clues for avoiding the prophecy.
悪ぃが　この俺は　そう簡単に…。 簡単に…。
What do we do? Now that we know Kurapika's secret, it's dangerous to wait around.
あれ？　あぁ！
If Nobunaga captures either Gon or me again, we probably won't be able to escape.
うっ！　てめぇ…。
But we have Kurapika with us now.
矢には　即効性の しびれ薬が塗ってある。
We should take them out before they have a chance
to recover and escape.
１週間は まともに歩くこともできないよ。
We know where their current base is.
安心しな！ 水場は　すぐ　そばにある。
If we take too long, they might get away.
死にはしないさ。
We need to move fast.
すごい
They could be making an
escape as we speak.
完全に気配を断って
We don't have time for too much thought.
獲物に近づき　機をうかがう やられたほうだって 矢を射る瞬間の殺気を感じて
The woman you mentioned
is certainly a threat...
素早く　よけて 致命傷にはならなかった でも　それすらも予測して
But since their leader is dead, I'll do as Gon says, and focus on
recovering my brethren's eyes.
あらかじめ 矢に毒を塗ってあった
Seriously?! Yeah. You're sure about this?
これが　ハント！
Kurapika's made up his mind. We can't force him to change it.
もし　今の俺がヒソカから プレートを奪えるとしたら
Sorry, Killua. Thank you for the valuable information.
まず　気づかれないように 近づいて…
The dead bodies were fakes.
隙を見て 奪う！
Kurapika?
よっしゃあ！
Huh? You mean the dead bodies
of the Troupe members?
この的と違って ヒソカは動くんだよねぇ
It would be possible for a
Conjurer to accomplish that. Damn!
うん…
Why didn't I realize this sooner?
どうしたって　一発勝負
What now?
一瞬の隙を突いて ヒソカのプレートを
We're here to help. Uh-huh.
この針で 取らなくちゃ　ダメなんだ！
Yeah.
よし！
Kurapika, it's me.
相手の動きを読んで…
The community has called off the hunt
for the remaining Troupe members. What? We've learned that they
came from Meteor City.
そこだ！
The Troupe comes from Meteor City?
うん　何か違うなぁ。
The reward has been rescinded? Seriously?
規則正しく 揺れてるだけの的だと
The Troupe comes from Meteor City.
簡単に動きが読めちゃうもんなぁ。
Makes sense... That explains why their
identities are still unknown, and why the cops haven't
been able to catch them.
あっ　そっか…。 ヒソカが　よけることも 考えなきゃね。
What's Meteor City? A city populated by people who,
as far as society is concerned, don't exist. There's a city like that?
これで 飛んでる鳥の動きを読んで 捕らえることができなきゃ
It began as a dump over 1,500 years ago.
ヒソカからプレートなんか 奪えっこない！
People began to live off the garbage that was dumped there.
えいっ。
From garbage to weapons, and even people.
ありゃ…。
will accept anything left there.
なに　１回や２回で うまく行くはずないもんね。 ダァ！　それ！　えいっ。
I've heard that Meteor City
residents share a bond thinner than that between strangers,
stronger than that between family.
一体　こりゃ　誰の番号だ？
with weapons and precious metals
under the pretext of garbage. That would be the Mafia community.
もうすぐ　日が暮れる。 明日の朝まで あまり動かぬほうがいいか…。
But the Mafia is hunting the Troupe! In return, the Mafia recruited
people from Meteor City.
ハァハァ…。
People who didn't exist, as far
as society was concerned. Perfect for committing crimes.
ハァ…　クソ！
The Troupe destroyed the
normally intimate relationship
こんなに難しいとは思わなかった。
between the Mafia community and Meteor City.
こう暗くちゃ　よく見えないし 鳥も　いなくなっちゃったなぁ。
But the Mafia has decided to
prioritize that relationship.
さぁ　今日も特訓だ！
A red-eyed customer will visit your shop, half angel, half death-bringer.
タァ！ トリャ！
You would do well to sell
the calendar's secrets.
はっ…　えい！ タァ！　えい！　はっ。
He will be especially pleased to
learn the eleventh moon's secret.
ハァハァ…。
The customer will return on a hot day, leaving you alone with a man
bearing St. Peter's cross.
ダメだ やっぱり無理なのかなぁ。 自由に飛び回る鳥を
The false fourth moon will be
torn away from the calendar.
ピンポイントで 捕らえるなんてさぁ。
Only six pages remain.
あっ。
What does your fortune say?
行く！
Look at this, everyone!
そうか…
That would be our secrets, right?
あったぞ！
Hisoka, what is this?
相手の動きが読める瞬間が！
Lemme see!
今だ！
The eleven-legged spider grows homesick, losing five more legs.
やった！
Do not leave your temporary shelter, for you are one of the remaining legs.
分ったぞ！ 相手が獲物を捕らえる瞬間
Hisoka...
そこを狙うんだ！
Did you sell him out?
フッ ついに　マスターしたか…
Sell out Uvo?!
だが その集中力が　あだとなる フッ…
Hisoka's fortune changed when
it was passed to Pakunoda.
ついに　ヒソカを狩る 会心の技を身につけたゴン
What could that mean?